year,
Once a
in alone.
went
I
the high priest.
am
I
of Atonement
Day
On the
aside my gold,
laid
I
white linen,
plain
put on
blood behind the
carried
and
veil
where
dark
into the thick
dwelt.
God
us:
warned
He had
not:
die
"that he
in
appear
for I will
upon the mercy
cloud
the
seat."
goats
two
They gave me
offering.
sin
for one
I killed,
first
The
its blood before
sprinkled
and
seat.
mercy
the
alive
The second I kept
both my hands
laid
I
head,
on its
over it every sin
confessed
people,
of the
into
away
and sent it
wilderness,
the
it all where
carry
to
be found.
never
it would
goats.
Two
died.
One
it away.
carried
One
this for forty
did
I
years
Whose
knew
and never
I was casting.
shadow
Then,
away,
far
a
died outside the city
Man
wall
of the
veil
and the
in two,
tore
temple
bottom,
from top to
hand.
human
by no
he
blood
"By his own
in once into the
entered
place,
holy
obtained eternal redemption for
having
us."
understood.
And at last I
goats
both
He was
that paid,
blood
the
carried
and the One who
away.
it
High
true
He was the
Priest.
was
work
And when His
finished,
down.
sat
He
I feared is
veil
The
torn.
in is open.
way
The
not come to
do
So
me.
not come to a
Do
goat,
altar.
yearly
or a
Jesus
Come to
your sin away,
carried
He
as the east
far
as
west.
is from the
to Him,
Come
clean.
carried
and be